<plugin>
	<title>NewsTicker</title>
	<filename>newsticker.swf</filename>
	<version>1.3</version>
	<compatibility>Compatible with 5.0+</compatibility>
	<author>Ethan Feldman</author>
	<description>
	This plugin creates a block of scrolling text on the player, similar to a news ticker.
	You can set the text with the flashvar newsticker.text.
	You can set the speed at which the text scrolls with the flashvar newsticker.scrollspeed.
	By default, the text scrolls from right to left, but you can reverse it by adding a - sign in front of the flashvar.
	You can set the position and size with the newsticker.position and newsticker.size flashvars.
	You can use the player's lightcolor flashvar to change the text color, 
	and the player's frontcolor flashvar to change the background of the ticker.
	By default the background is gray, and the text is yellow.
	You can set a link for the text, which will open in a new window, with the flashvar newsticker.link.
	You can set additional width for the text, with the flashvar newsticker.textwidth. It is the additional times to mutiply the width of the textbox.
	This plugin uses the player's dock. If you set the dock  flashvar to false, a button will show up on the control bar.
	If you mouse over the message, it will stop. Moving the mouse off of the message will resume the scrolling.
	This plugin now includes playlist support, using the jwplayer namespace. 
	You can set a new flashvar called newsticker.nobutton to remove the dock icon / controlbar icon.
	</description>
	<href>http://www.ethanfeldman.net/</href>
	<flashvars>
		<flashvar>
			<name>position</name>
			<default>over</default>
			<description>Position of the plugin.</description>
		</flashvar>
		<flashvar>
			<name>size</name>
			<default>0</default>
			<description>Width or height of the plugin when not in the over state</description>
		</flashvar>
		<flashvar>
			<name>text</name>
			<default>Hello, thanks for downloading...feel free to change this message...</default>
			<description>Text to add to the ticker</description>
		</flashvar>
		<flashvar>
			<name>scrollspeed</name>
			<default>3</default>
			<description>Speed to scroll the text.</description>
		</flashvar>
		<flashvar>
			<name>link</name>
			<default></default>
			<description>An optional link to go to when the text is clicked on</description>
		</flashvar>
		<flashvar>
			<name>textwidth</name>
			<default>1</default>
			<description>Additional times to mutiply the width of the textbox.</description>
		</flashvar>
		<flashvar>
			<name>nobutton</name>
			<default>false</default>
			<description>Set this to true if you want no dock icon / controlbar button.</description>
		</flashvar>
	</flashvars>
</plugin>